comic-rocket.com 2016-04-02

# Privacy - Comic Rocket webcomic list

## Privacy

* * *

**Privacy Policy**

**Comic Rocket Commitment to Privacy**

Comic Rocket is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following Privacy Policy to protect the personal information you provide us online. This Privacy Policy applies only to our Site at [www.comic-rocket.com](http://www.comic-rocket.com/) (“Site”) and information collected for us or by us through our Site and through various features and online offerings on our Site. It does not apply to any third party site or service linked to our Site or recommended or referred by our Site or by our staff. Further, it does not apply to any other Site or online service operated by Zinofile, Inc. dba Comic Rocket, or to any of our offline activities.  Questions regarding this policy should be directed to info@comic-rocket.com

**Collection and Use of Information**

Comic Rocket collects three different types of information through the Site: personally identifiable information needed for site operations, information that users choose to make public, and anonymous information.

Personally Identifiable Information Needed for Site Operations: Comic Rocket will only collect your personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, or telephone number) if you provide it voluntarily. If you do not want this information to be collected by us, please do not submit it. Comic Rocket will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purpose for which it is collected.  We only use the personally identifiable information which is provided through our Site to help us improve our services to you, to provide you with the products and services you have requested, to inform you about additional products or services that may be of interest to you, for marketing purposes and for other internal purposes. Comic Rocket occasionally may hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending mail and processing event registration. Comic Rocket will only provide these companies with the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. If after providing Comic Rocket with personally identifiable information,  you do not wish to receive marketing and similar promotional communications from Comic Rocket, please contact us at [info@comic-rocket.com](mailto:info@comic-rocket.com)

Other than what is described, Comic Rocket does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others outside of Comic Rocket companies and their advertising and promotional agencies and consultants.  Comic Rocket will never give or sell your personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties to be used for the purposes of sending you unsolicited commercial offers (such as spam).   At any time, while accessing our site, any user, while online, may decline participation in any activity that asks for information (i.e. survey email, or ecommerce). Your choice not to participate will in no way affect your ability to use any other feature on our site.

Comic Rocket may also need to contact you for purposes other than marketing, for example to provide notice about the status of the Comic Rocket Site or the specific products or services you have requested. We also use this information to the extent necessary to enforce our Site terms of service and to prevent imminent harm to persons or property.  You may not opt-out of these kinds of communications.  Consistent with our change policy (see Your Consent and Notification of Changes below), we will post any updates or notices about material changes in our policies on collection and use of your personally identifiable information to this Privacy Policy page and other places we deem appropriate for notifying our visitors and customers of the changes.

Please note that notwithstanding our general nondisclosure policy, Comic Rocket will disclose personally identifiable information when required by law, or if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us, (b) protect and defend our rights, or (c) protect the rights, property, and other interests of our users or others.

**Information That Users Choose to Make Public**

Our Site includes various social networking and sharing features that allow users to make information public.  Anything that you specifically ask us to make public (your comics reading list, your recommendations, links to your facebook profile, etc.) we may make public.  Opting into such services on the Site is entirely voluntary.  If you choose to opt into such services on the Site, you expressly give us permission to make the information – including, where relevant, personally identifable information – public.  In addition, to the extent that you post public comments, reviews, etc. on the Site, you expressly give Zinofile, Inc. dba Comic Rocket a license to use that information (please see Section 6 of our ** Terms of Use ** for details).

Anonymous Information:  In addition, in the course of using our site we automatically track certain anonymous, aggregate information about your visit to the Comic Rocket Site. This information may include, for example, the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you go to next (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address. Many sites automatically collect this information. The anonymous information that we do collect from your visit is never linked to any of your personally identifiable information until you voluntarily submit that personal information. We use the anonymous information in the aggregate for purposes such as to generate statistical reports about the use of our Site or to improve the quality of our Service.  We may provide this anonymous information to other parties or use it internally.  Our use of this anonymous information about how our visitors and customers interact with the Service is not restricted in any way other than it is and remains in a form that is not linked to any personally identifiable information or otherwise identifies any particular visitor or customer.

We also employ the use of cookies to assist us in this process. A cookie is a small piece of computer code that enables web servers to identify users. Cookies do not store any personally identifiable information that you have provided to our site. You have the ability to delete cookie files from your hard drive at any time or avoid cookies by configuring your browser to reject them or to notify you when a cookie is being placed on your hard drive.

**Security**

Comic Rocket has implemented a number of security features throughout the Comic Rocket site to prevent the unauthorized release of or access to personal information. For example, passwords are stored in industry-standard hashed form, and backups containing personally-identifiable information are encrypted. Please be advised, however, that although Comic Rocket has endeavored to create a secure and reliable site for you, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to or from Comic Rocket via the Comic Rocket site or e-mail cannot be guaranteed. When disclosing any personal information, you should remain mindful of the fact that it is potentially accessible to the public, and consequently, can be collected and used by others without your consent. Comic Rocket has no responsibility or liability for the security of information transmitted via the Internet.

**External Web Sites**

To the extent hyperlinks or banner advertisements incorporating hyperlinks are utilized to access third party sites, you should be aware that these third party web sites are not controlled by Comic Rocket and, therefore, are not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should check the privacy policies of these individual sites to see how your personal information will be utilized by the operators of those third party web sites.

**Changes to Comic Rocket’s Business**

In the event Comic Rocket goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, our customers’ personally identifiable information may be part of the assets transferred.  The information transferred or shared remains subject to the promises made in this Privacy Policy, unless you agree to new terms.

**Your Consent and Notification of Changes**

By using our Site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Comic Rocket. Comic Rocket may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to make a material change in our Privacy Policy, we will post that change on this page and on any other pages or locations we deem important to alert you about the change in our privacy and information collection practices . Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept these changes. In some cases, we may attempt to contact you through an email or other address you have provided to give you information and choices about our using your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection.  In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that affect your personally identifiable information already stored in our database, we apply those changes to the personally identifiable information in our possession only with your consent or as otherwise permitted by applicable law. 

**Changing Your Information and Opting Out**

You may have the right to access the personal information which Comic Rocket has collected about you. You may also have the right to modify any errors contained in that information. Please contact us for more details. Our Site provides visitors and customers the opportunity to opt-out of receiving specific types of communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor or customer. In addition, you may unsubscribe or opt out of all future communications from us that do not relate to the products and services you have ordered by removing your contact and personally identifiable information from our marketing and communications databases by clicking the unsubscribe link on any email marketing communication you receive.

**Further Information about Comic Rocket Privacy Policy and Practices**

This Privacy Policy applies to all visitors and customers of our Site. If you become an inactive customer, or if we close or suspend your account, we will continue to adhere to the Privacy Policy in place when we collected your personally identifiable information so long as we retain it in our databases.  We may delete any or all of your information at any time without notice to you for any reason or no reason unless otherwise required by law to retain it.  You may have other privacy protections under state laws and we will comply with any applicable state laws when we disclose information about you. This Privacy Policy replaces our previous policy on this topic and any statements or disclosures to you about our information practices.

**How to Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at info@comic-rocket.com

Copyright © 2012 Comic Rocket. All rights reserved.  This version of the Comic Rocket Privacy Policy is effective August 1, 2012
